# ADNAN PAWNE Account Executive

+91 88067 49614 / adnanpawne97@gmail.com / www.linkedin.com/in/adnan-pawne

Samar Apartment, Almas Colony Rd., Kausa, Mumbra

### **OBJECTIVE**

Having worked in the financial industry for five years, I am capable of Collecting and analyzing financial data to provide management reports. Work effectively with the team and top management by having a thorough awareness of team spirit. Looking for an executive position to utilize my data visualization and reporting skills.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Accountant JAN 2021 – DEC 2022

#### Mount Meru India Pvt. Ltd., Andheri

In-charge of establishing and maintaining masters and the General Ledger in accordance with the chart of accounts. Organizing multiple reports like bank and cash reports, loans and borrowing, procurement reports. Automation of data on Google Sheets, and management reports on credit control. Accountable for determining any credit limit. Data Visualization Using PowerBI for Sales and Inventory report. Creating contacts and products in Odoo, as well as generating purchase orders A.K.A. the Chart of Accounts and other financial reports in Odoo.

Accounts Assistance JULY 2019 – JUNE 2020

#### Amol Hande And Associates, Mumbai

Bank reconciliation, GST return filing, TDS calculation, income tax return filing, account preparation for multiple associations, responsibility for any deposit or withdrawal from the branch as well as bank accounts.

Account Assistance AUG 2017 – JULY 2018

#### India Trading Company, Ratnagiri

Data entry, bank reconciliation, calculating GST summaries, working with a chartered accountant, helping to prepare the monthly reconciliation, and handling petty cash for the organization.

Account Trainee AUG 2016 – APRIL 2017

#### M/s Oswal & Associates, Ratnagiri

Sales and purchase entries, maintaining Excel trial balance, calculation of the VAT summary-2016, bank auditing for new account openings, Verification of Loans Statements, and participation in an internal audit to get ready for a third-party audit.

# **EDUCATION**

MUMBAI UNIVERSITYAPRIL 2019Bachelor Of Commerce (B.Com)Ratnagiri

INSTITUTE OF COST ACCOUNTANTS OF INDIA

REGD. NO.: 01212128395

PURSUING

MUMBAI

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Microsoft Power BI
- MS Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint)
- TALLY (ERP9, Prime), TDL, WINMAN, Odoo, Google sheet
- Known Languages like English, Hindi, Marathi, Urdu